Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory4 Mss.B.B61.inventory04
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents D
  - Deckert, E. (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 14
  - De Cora, Angel (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 17
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, ? Apr. 31; ?
  - Defaut, A. (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1927 July; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 31; ?
  - De Forest, Robert W. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1907 May 11; 4p
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 20
      - see Boas, F. to Nuttall, Zelia, 1928 Oct. 17; 2p
  - Defram, H. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1919 July 16; 1p
  - Degginger, F. (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1928 June 27; 2p
  - Deglman, G. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 13; 1p
      - see FB to Tyler, J.M., 1919 Nov. 13
  - Dehego, J.M. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 20
  - Dehmel, H. (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 6; 3p
  - Dehn, E. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 19; 1p
  - Deiler, J. Hanno (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 1; 1p
  - Deitzgen Eugene & Co. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1927 May 17; 1p
  - Dekeyser, Leon (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 11; 1p
  - Delano, Frederick A. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1942 May 4
    - To Boas, 1942 May 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 May 6; 1p
  - Delich, E.S. (Box 20)
    - To Keppel, 1906 Aug. 15
  - Delitzsch, Frederick (Box 20)
    - 1905 May 15, 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 14, Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 4; 4p
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 June 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 June 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Sep. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 21; 3p
    - See Germanistic Soc. of Am., 1920 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 19
  - Dell, Floyd (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 3; 1p
  - Dellenbaugh, F.S. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 11; 1p
    - From Ogden, R., 1927 Dec. 22
  - Deloria, Ella C., 10.0 folders (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 June 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Aug. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sep. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 May 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Sep. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Sep. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 May 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 June 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 June 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 26; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 28; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 25; 8p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 Aug. 21; 4p
    - To Boas, 1928 Sep. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, ? Dec. 31; 4p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 7; 5p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 July 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 11; 4p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 25; 6p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 7; 4p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1p
      Letters in this location labeled "Tuesday Eve," and "Sunday Eve."
    - To Boas, ? Dec. 31; 1p
    - see FB open letter, 1937 July 7
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 June 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1938 June 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, ? Dec. 31; 3p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 12; 3p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Sep. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 26; 4p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 July 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 7; 4p
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Sep. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 June 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 July 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 15; 2p
    - To Beckwith, M.W., 1926 Nov. 11; 1p
    - From Clark, D.W., 1930 Nov. 6
    - From Harrington, J. P., 1939 May 6
    - From Nute, Grace Lee, 1942 Nov. 13; 2p
  - Deloria, V.V. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 25; 1p
  - Demetracopoulou, D. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 10; 1p
  - De Meyer, M. (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 12; 2p
  - Demion, A.H. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 26; 3p
  - Democracy and Intellectual Freedom, Amer. Committee of (Box 21)
    - 1939 Oct. 14, 17p
    - 1939 Oct. 31, ?
      see also Amer. Committee for D & IF
      Univ. Federation for D & IF
  - Demos, Paul (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 3; 1p
  - Dempwolff, O. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Sep. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 30; 1p
  - Demsey Bill (Box 21)
    - 1940 Jan. 19, 1p
  - Dencker, J. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 7
  - Denig, R. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Sep. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 9; 2p
  - Denison (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 16
  - Denkschrift -- - errichtendes Institut Internat. philosoph. Zusammenarbeit (Box 21)
    - 1936 Dec. 31, ? 3p
  - Denney, J.W. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 25; 1p
  - Dennis, L.M. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p
  - Dennis, N.B. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 10
  - Dennis, Wayne (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 8; 1p
  - Denns, James (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1894 Jan. 20; 2p
  - Densmore, Frances (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 6; 1p
  - Dental Cosmos (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 24; 1p
      see Chandler, W.J.
  - Denver Turn-Verein (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 1; 1p
    - see FB to Germania Pres., 1905 Nov. 1
  - De Onis, Federico (DeOnes?) (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 30; 1pand
  - Derby, Geo. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 16
  - Derby, S.C. (Box 21)
    - To N.D.C. Hodges, 1887 June 7
  - Deretchin, J. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 10
  - Derounian, Arthur (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 29; 1p
  - Derviss, C.T. (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1905 June 30
  - Désir, Herman L. (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 31; ? 2p
  - Detroit Journal (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 18
  - Detroit News (Box 21)
    - Fr -- To Boas, 1914 Dec. 18
  - Dettman, James (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 6; 1p
  - Detwiler, S.R. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 11; 1p
  - Deuel, T. (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 25; 2p
    - see Goodchild D., 1930 Feb. 15
  - Deupig (?), Kurt (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1907 June 13
  - Deutsch, Bernard S. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1933 July 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 June 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 6; 1p
  - Deutsch, G. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 22; 1p
  - Deutsch, Monroe E. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 11; 1p
  - Deutschamerikanischer Kulturverband (Box 21)
    - 1938 Oct 10, 1p
    - 1940 Jan. 30, ? 2p
    - 1940 Feb. 25, 3p
    - 1941 Dec. 31, ?
    - 1938 Dec 17
    - 1938 Dec?
    - 1941 Dec 12
  - Deutsche Akademie (Box 21)
    - 1929 June 6, 4p
    - see Rohrbach, P., 1929 Dec. 31; ?
    - see Rohrbach, P., 1930 Oct. 16; 3p
    - see Rohrbach, P., 1930 Oct. 18; 3p
    - see Fehn, R., 1931 Nov. 30; ?
    - from Miller, K.A., 1933 Aug. 19
    - from Meyer, A.O., 1934 Dec. 31; ?
    - from Meyer, A.O., 1933 Jul. 8
    - from Meyer, A.O., 1934 Dec. 21
  - Deutsche Bucherei (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 3; 1p
  - Deutsche Literaturzeitung (Box 21)
    see Hinneberg, Paul
  - Deutsche Polar Kommission (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1885 Aug. 19; 2p
  - Deutscher Gesellig-Wissenschaftlicher Verein von New York (Box 21)
    - 1887 Nov. 21
    - 1895 Dec. 18
  - Deutsches Archaeologisches Institut (Box 21)
    see Rodenwaldt, Gerh.
  - Deutsches Auslands-Sekretariat (Box 21)
    - 1921 Apr. 6, 3p
  - Deutsches Theater zu Berlin (Box 21)
    see Gersdorf, Baron C.L. von
  - Deutschmann (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 18
  - Deville, E. (Box 21)
    - 1888 Jan. 10
  - Devine, Edward T. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 21; 3p
    - From Boas, -- May 6
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1905 May 5
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 14
    - From Walton, E., 1905 Mar. 29
  - Devoe & Reynolds (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1927 May 4; 1p
  - Dewey, Davis R. (Box 21)
    Folder missing 9194. Copy made from F#1308 in place.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 31; 1p
  - Dewey, John (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 27
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 28
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 5
    - From Boas, 1916 Mar. 29; 4p
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 12
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 17; 1p
    - also see FB to Butler, N.M., 1939 Jan. 17
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 23
    - see FB to Woodworth, R.S., 1931 Sep. 2
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 30; 1p
    - see FB open letter re Spain, 1938 Jan.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 12; 3p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 21; 2p
    - To Comité Nobel du Palriement Norweg. re Peace prize, 1936 Jan. 31; ? 1p
    - see Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas, 1937 Feb. 11
    - see Wiener, Phil. P., 1938 Nov. 30
    - From Schlick, M., 1936 Jan. 25
  - Dewey, Lucy A. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 31; 1p
  - Dewey, M. (Box 21)
    - To Gies, W.J., 1918 Mar. 23; 1p
  - The Dial (Dial Publishing Co.) (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1919 July 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 2 and 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p
      also see Aikin, R.P.
  - Diaz, Pedro (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 2; 2p
  - Diaz Lernhdo, Miguel (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1912 Jan. 21; 2p
  - Dice, Lee R. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 16; 2p
  - Dickey, F.A. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Sep. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 May 8
    - To Boas, 1917 May 22
  - Dickler, Richard (Box 21)
    - see Spencer, Louise C., 1940 Feb. 24
  - B. Dickson & Co. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1909 May 28
    - From Boas, 1909 June 25
    - To Boas, 1908 June 24
  - Dickson, C.T. (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 5
  - Dickstein, Samuel (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 10; 3p
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 14; 1p
    - To Celler, E., 1938 Apr. 13; 1p
    - From Celler, E., 1938 Apr. 12
  - Dieckmann, C. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 17; 1p
  - Diedrick, H.M. (Box 21)
    - To Keppel, 1906 Aug. 13
  - Diehl (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1938 Aug. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Aug. 30; 1p
  - Dietch (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 28; 1p
  - Dietrich Reimer / Ernst Vohsen (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 26; 1p
  - Dijour, Miss Elisabeth (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 July 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Sep. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Sep. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 June 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 July 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Sep. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 July 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 8; 4p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 14; 4p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Sep. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 25; 4p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 17; 2p
      - enc. Les Matako du Chaco, 1933 July 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 24; 2p
    - From Jones, A.L., 1931 May 16
  - Dill, A.G. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1936 May 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 26; 1p
  - Dilliard, Irving (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 25; 1p
  - Dillingham, Sen. Wm. P. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1910 June 17
  - Dillon, Mrs. H.N. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1931 June 29; 1p
  - Dimler, F.J. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 25; 1p
  - Dinwiddie (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1900 Sep. 30
  - Dinwiddie, A.B. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 15; 1p
  - Dionne, N.E. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1906 Sep. 18
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 5
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 22
    - From Boas, 1907 May 1
    - From Boas, 1907 May 6
    - From Boas, 1907 May 25
    - From Boas, 1907 Jun. 1
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 21
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 21; 3p
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 May 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 May 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 May 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 May 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 May 30; 4p
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 13; 4p
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 13
  - Dipsolu, A.B. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1937 June 8; 1p
  - Dipsolu, A. de (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1936 July 8; 1p
  - Ditchburn, W.E. (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 3; 1p
    - From Fairbairn, A.M.D., 1930 Dec. 19, Dec. 8
    - From Halliday, W.H., 1930 Nov. 18
    - From Halliday, W.H., 1930 Dec. 6
    - To Brit. Columbia Gov., 1930 Dec. 5
    - To R. Bruce, 1930 Dec. 13; 1p
  - Ditman, Norman E. (Box 21)
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 27
  - Ditman, L.T. (Box 21)
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 10
  - Dix, Lester A. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 30; 1p
  - Dixon, Roland B. (Box 22)
    - From Boas, 1902 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 31
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1906 June 4
    - From Boas, 1906 Sep. 24
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1907 May 21
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 26
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 31
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 6
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 11
    - From Boas, 1908 June 11
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 5
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 20; 3p
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 30
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 25
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 10
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 12
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 14
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 23
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 28
    - From Boas, 1909 May 11
    - From Boas, 1909 May 20
    - From Boas, 1909 June 9
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 3
    - also see FB to Gordon, G.B., 1909 Nov. 11
    - From Boas, 1909 Nov. 19
    - also see FB to Butler, N.M., 1909 Nov. 26
    - Boas -- to Dixon, 1909 Dec. 10
      (is on reverse of p. 1 of Boas to Damrosch, 31 March 1920)
    - also see FB to Butler, N.M., 1909 Dec. 19
    - also see FB to Butler, N.M., 1911 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 27
    - also see FB to Chávez, E.A., 1911 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1911 May 11
    - From Boas, 1911 May 18
    - From Boas, 1911 May 20
    - From Boas, 1911 June 8
    - From Boas, 1911 June 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Dec. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 27; 4pand1p
    - Also see FB to Chavez, E., 1913 Aug. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 16
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 10 & 27
    - Also see FB to Cutting, B., 1914 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 9
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1914 May 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Sep. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 26
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 29
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 3 and 6
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 28
      - also see FB to Gordon, G., 1916 May 22
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 3 and 6
      - Also to Goddard, Kroeber, Lowie, Goldenweiser, Hooton, Savelle, MacCurdy, Wessler, Holmes, Hough, Hrdlicks, Gordon, Speck, Hodge, Tozzer, Getteking, 1916 Dec. 8
    - Also to Kroeber, Tozzer, Goddard, 1917 Sep. 14
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 9; 1p